This week, every famous investor in
America published their investment
portfolios for the world to see. We're
talking about over $200 billion worth of
investments across the entire AI stack
from the likes of Warren Buffett, Ray
Dalio, and even our good friend Leopold,
Ashen Brother. And at surface value, it
might look like it's quite bearish. They
sold a lot of major stocks, including
Nvidia, and some memory stocks as well.
But if you look carefully, there's two
specific layers within the AI theme that
they've not only doubled down on, but
have increased the pie. There's never
been more money in the AI sphere before.
And we're going to unpack all of these
and more on today's episode. There was
an episode that we recorded on July 31st
in reference to Leopold's 13F where we
said his next 13F filing is going to be
one of the most exciting episodes of all
time. And listen, we are here.
>> It's exciting. It's guaranteed. I will
say it's not exactly how we imagined
this forecast going because what we're
looking at here is basically a memorial
memorial memorial. How do you say it?
when someone died like Leopold
>> moratorium.
Yes, that's what we're looking at. We're
looking at a sheet of paper from a
company that no longer exists because as
we know Leopold was liquidated
tragically. Now 13F we might want to
start there just so you kind of have an
idea of what's going on here. Basically
any company that trades equities over
$100 million must disclose their
positions quarterly within 45 days of
the quarter end. So, what we're looking
at here and throughout this episode is
what those snapshots look like across
all the top investment firms in the
country and in the world. And we're
going to try to derive some conclusions
from that. But to start, we have to go
to Leopold's portfolio because
everyone's going to want to know what
were the stocks that he was in that blew
him up because as we know from the
previous episode, which if you haven't
watched, I highly suggest uh the Wall
Street darling um no longer owns public
positions. And it's because we have some
numbers and it looks like the largest
holding by far was uh SanDisk and
Micron. He was very much memory pilled.
I think the tough thing about this is
like directionally I think he was
correct. He just got totally liquidated.
But Sandis position was 28.5% of the
book. He had Micron at 28% of the book.
And then I mean together that's over
half of the book is in Micron. And then
there's Bloom Energy at 9 and a half%.
We know how much he was up on that. We
have TSMC, Nebia core, we have a couple
of the Neoclouds. and then everything
else combines for about 18% of the
portfolio. So he was heavily heavily
heavily involved in these memory stocks.
We know he was using some leverage and
it appears as if that's what blew him
up. Yeah. So the saddest part about this
is probably all of these positions have
been decimated. I I saw rumors I think
it reported from Bloomberg about a week
ago that he now has a casual uh you know
500 to a billion dollar uh open equity
position but the majority still lies in
his anthropic stake for now. But uh I
think if we look at the Leopole thesis
in general which was doubling down on AI
infrastructure particularly in memory
and neoclouds that thesis is still very
alive and well and and let's like pause
and uh on the memory position. It's had
a pretty rocky month. If you remember I
think 2 weeks ago we were reporting on
SKH he reporting their best quarterly
earnings ever. They made more money in a
single quarter than they did in an
entire year last year, but their stock
tanked about 20% the preceding week. And
so the thesis behind that was people
thought that memory investors were too
overleveraged and that we were reaching
a top where GPU infrastructure, Nvidia
and all the people that were buying
memory could not want to buy more
memory. Recent news has been revealed
from SanDisk uh over their investing day
that not only is that not true, but all
these major investors that we're going
to be covering in this episode today
have doubled down and bought more,
especially at the lows recently. And
also SanDisk in particular has developed
this new type of memory. It's called
high bandwidth flash. And I just want to
take like 20 seconds to to describe what
this is. There's a couple different
types of memory. There's DRAM, which is
like your standard memory type. There's
HBM which is your high bandwidth memory
which is specialized for AI GPU
specifically and then there's this thing
called high bandwidth flash which is
this new thing which was created by
SanDisk and honestly dominated by them
and it's used for like inference mainly
and inference recently has become like
the major trend in AI it's actually
consuming so much capex spend for the
hyperscalers from Google Amazon and the
likes and so SanDisk in particular
stands to benefit the most from this and
they have this new memory type which is
being ordered or backlogged already into
the end of 2027. So this is a new
revenue opportunity for them and we
haven't seen exceeding demand like this
ever before. So the point is memory the
memory argument is still very strong and
Leopold was right. He just he was too
over 11 man. That's the tragic part is
like the the thesis is coherent and it
still stands and there was nothing wrong
about his positions or his like
directional ideas of where the market
was going. He just did it all wrong
because he was using improper position
sizing and most importantly leverage. I
mean, this is what happens when you use
leverage. Everybody knows this. So, I
think it's an interesting peak into what
could have been. Like, directionally,
the stock names look strong. It's just
the way he positioned didn't look nearly
as strong. There is another company who
reported their 13F this week that I
think it's worth highlighting. Who is
when you think of the strongest, they're
about as strong as it gets. These people
have been around forever. This is Warren
Buffett's Birkshshire Hathaway. They are
always really interesting because they
move in a way similar to the way Apple
does. They move very slow. They're
normally the last mover. When they do
so, they do so with a tremendous amount
of size and conviction. Now, as we know,
Birkshshire Hathway is no longer run by
Warren Buffett. Unfortunately, no longer
run by Charlie Monger either. And Greg
Ael is now at the helm of this. So, Greg
Ael is the new guy in charge. And he has
joined Birksher and has begun deploying
capital at pretty high rates. The
biggest ad of the quarter, which was 17
billion added, was for Google or
Alphabet, which was really surprising to
see because why would they be buying
Google instead of buying the memory
companies? And I think we we have like a
thesis. I'll cover the rest first before
we get into why, but it looks like
they've added 44% of Delta of Macy's of
LAR. So, they're very much moving
towards a this is kind of like the
Joshua Kushner thing where they're like,
"Okay, who's been around forever and
then who's going to win on the frontier
and that feels like kind of how Warren
Buffett and Bergkshire are placing
themselves here." But the Google thing,
I want to talk about the Google thing,
EJ. Why are they buying so much Google?
So, I think it's a a thesis that you and
I have like been very fond of for over
like many years now. Google is the only
company on Earth that owns the entire
stack for AI. Now, I I just want to
emphasize like how important this is.
Like they're not only creators of AI
models, but they're also creators of
custom GPUs that run and train those AI
models. They're also creators of the
distribution platforms. The number one
in the world, by the way. You've got
Google Search, obviously. You've got
Gmail, you've got G Suite, you've got
Android, you've got so many different
Google products that distribute to
hundreds and hundreds of millions of
people every single day. So they have
the ultimate distribution platform, but
they also own all the infrastructure,
the power that is required to fund all
of this. And they have amazing amounts
of capex. I think Google actually this
year takes the crown for spending the
most. I think they're on track to spend
around $250 billion by the end of the
year. If Google is the only company that
owns or dominates across the entire
stack in AI, that is an amazing company
to own because they can fine-tune each
of the different layers for their
particular product. So why that's
important is let's say you look at
Google search data and you notice that
customers really like buying houses in a
specific area at this time of the year.
They can orient their own AI model to
produce and serve up adverts or
suggestions to people to shop in a
particular type of way. And that kind of
uniformity or like hyper specificity is
really hard to nail down if you are just
a model lab creator or if you're just a
GPU producer. So that's really powerful
for the thesis in general for Google.
Now my question to you Josh is do you
think this happened before the fallout
within Google when Damis stepped aside
Jeff Dean left. I I have a feeling it
is. So I wonder if they've cut down
their position since but I still think
Google's a good bet. Yeah, I would bet
this happened beforehand. And I would
bet that it's also not really going to
change their mind because I don't think
it materially affects the business. In
fact, it may be a positive. Um, it's
like I remember seeing this post from a
long time ago that was basically like
Google isn't taking themselves seriously
until they start firing the leadership
that put them in this position. And I
mean in a way that's kind of what's
happening here. The leadership who put
them in this position where they had all
the technology did not capitalize is
starting to rotate and cycle out. There
is fresh blood who I'm sure is very
hungry. Sergey Brin is back. He is kind
of in wartime mode. And I mean Google is
this remarkably incredible business. And
what we're going to find as we go
through the remaining 13F filings here
is that I mean spoiler alert the two
biggest winners this quarter are Amazon
and Google. Everyone loves the
hyperscalers. Everyone loves the people
who are spending huge amounts of capex
because it's easy for them to project
revenues. For these newer companies when
they spend a lot of money it's high
risk. They haven't proven their revenue
over time. But in the case of Google
they're projecting unbelievable margins
on their Google cloud services. They
have the increasing capability of
building their own hardware chips like
their TPUs and their ironwoods that they
have and they have this entire ecosystem
that they've built with a very strong
moat and it seems like that's not going
anywhere anytime soon. So Google is just
this unbelievable business. Same thing
with Amazon. They're companies with huge
amounts of capital on their balance
sheets. They're companies that are
spending it.
>> These things are pretty underpriced,
man. They're they're pretty underpriced
>> on a relative basis. They're not trading
at a very high multiple even though
they're the only companies with proven
track records that are showing quarter
over quarter. Hey, we're spending all
this capex, but look at the returns that
we've had on this capex. There's this
amazing stat about Google. And I have no
idea what these specifics are, but I
remember reading it and being like, "Oh
my god, this is so right." Where every
dollar Google invested yielded say like
$2.8 in return or something like that
where since since the inception of the
company. So when you hear a company like
Google who is one of the best capital
allocators in the world over the course
of the last three decades saying not
only are we going to spend a lot of
money, we're going to spend a record
amount of money because we are so high
conviction that these investments will
pay off in the long run. I think you got
to get pretty excited about that because
as a capital allocator there's not many
people better than Google. So that is
why I presume Birkshere we see uh taking
a pretty large position in this. But now
we have to move over to what feels like
home for us. I think this is the uh Brad
Gersner, the Gavin Baker, the Nvidia
portfolio. These are what the the
companies that I think like when we
think of the companies we want to invest
in, this feels most true to me at least.
Uh the number one holding of all of
them, Nvidia, like $2 billion is just
crazy. It's like $ 1.9 billion. They
have second for Brad Gersonner is
Cerebras at 1.6 billion. Then there's
Meta, TSM, Cororeweave, ARM. Gavin Baker
on the other hand, $4.7 billion position
in SpaceX. then Micron, Cerebras, Aster
Labs, Sienna, and Credo. Those bottom
ones I don't even recognize. But that's
kind of how we could think of the top
two perhaps like Twitter traders, the
the top traders on X, here's kind of the
position that they find themselves in.
Yeah. I mean, if I were to bucket these
investors in a particular group, it's
like the forward-looking group, right?
They're like the higher risk takers, but
they're playing with like much bigger
capital allocations. It's funny you
mentioned the the SpaceX 4.6 billion
position from Gavin Baker. this was his
biggest win. I I was listening to a
podcast of him on the All-In um show
just yesterday and he was basically
like, "Yeah, this is like one of my
biggest winnings, but like what I'm most
excited about right now is the power and
optics trade, which seemingly is a big
theme amongst these particular investors
in particular. So, just to give you a
kind of like lay of the land, when you
invest in AI, the typical names that
people look at are things like Nvidia.
or they look at some of the hyperscalers
that were mentioned already which is
like Google and Amazon and then if you
kind of dig a layer deeper they're like
oh no all these guys are going to need a
lot of memory so you invest in the likes
of SanDisk Micron SKH highix these are
names that we've already mentioned on
the show multiple times before but
something that we haven't really opined
on is this idea of power so if you have
all these expensive GPUs that Nvidia is
making if you have all this memory to
make these GPUs you still need power to
turn these things on but also there is
tons of data that these GPUs are
generating that they need to kind of
like transfer between these GPUs and
that's something that Gavin Baker
specifically has identified really early
on and he's winning quite a lot through
the likes of companies like Coherent
Corp. So let me explain sort of very
quickly why this is important. So if you
look at the sector of uh photonix which
basically means light when you have a
ton of GPUs in your data centers it gets
really arduous to transfer data between
these GPUs especially if you like rack
up like hundreds of thousands to
millions of GPUs which is like what Elon
Musk is basically doing right now. The
way to transfer data between GPUs is
using copper wires and it uses
electricity. It's pretty good. It's been
used for like decades now at this point,
but we've reached a point where there's
so many GPUs that it becomes incredibly
inefficient and cost inefficient as
well. So, you waste power and you waste
a lot of money. The solution to this is
basically using light and you heard me
correctly like literal light to transfer
data and this solves a problem where
it's much much cheaper and you can
transfer data at rapid speeds over very
great lengths and the only way to do
this is through companies like coherent
through companies like Genova who
basically create the materials and the
kind of like tiny infrastructure tools
that kind of like latch onto your GPUs
that'll allow yourself to do this and
we've seen this trade become quite
consensus over the year so far. You look
at Kheron Group is kind of like one of
the major manufacturers here which Gavin
Baker has taken a pretty big position in
and year to date they're up 85%. Um if
you look at this position actually here
on our artifact that we have here he's
taken a major position in Astra Labs
which helps with the interconnects
between GPUs. So basically like the
plumbing the wiring the ability to
transfer tons of data and information
across these GPUs is where all the money
has been flowing. And it's not just a
Gavin Baker thing. It is a Brad
Gersonner thing. And it is pretty
similar across traditional investors as
well, including like Ray Dalia. So it's
cool to see and I think it's something
that I'm keeping my eye on quite
astutely actually. Yeah, you can kind of
see these companies based on their size
and their risky exposure going out the
curve. Like we have Birkshshire who's
right at the core. You're buying Amazon,
you're buying Google. Those types of
companies are going to be slower, more
steady growth, much more stable. Then
there's people like Gavin, people like
Brad Gersonner. They're going the next
concentric circle out of this loop.
They're going to the infrastructure
layer. What is required in order to
generate tokens? It's optics. It's
memory. It's like going further and
further out the stack. That's kind of
what we're seeing with them and it has
been playing out really well. Another
thing I wanted to mention in Gavin's
portfolio is that he has a huge $2.3
billion position on QQQ puts. And for
those that aren't familiar, that
basically means he's buying the right to
own shares of the QQQ, which is
representative of the index, at the
current price, meaning it's insurance in
the case that it goes down. So I find
this interesting, too, and we saw this
with Leopold's portfolio as well, where
everyone has this, or not everyone, but
there are a few people that have this
hedge baked into their portfolios
currently, where if the market goes
down, they can still survive. They're
really just making a very specific,
hyperconentrated bet, in this case, on
AI hardware, the infrastructure layer.
So even if they're wrong, even if the
market does go down, but AI hardware
still continues to do well, they can
win. And I find it interesting that they
do have this hedge put in place, which
is kind of cool. There's also Nvidia,
which I found interesting. And
apparently they they also filed a 13F
because they I mean, as a company, they
own quite a bit of things. The first one
being Intel. They own $30 billion of
Intel, which is a pretty large position.
Yeah. I mean, good good place to be.
It's funny, you think of Intel and
Nvidia as like total competitors, but
Nvidia owns like quite a big chunk of
change in that company. Nvidia also has
a second biggest holding being SpaceX,
which we all know. I mean, this clearly
makes sense. SpaceX is going to be
exclusively buying Nvidia GPUs to power
all the new data centers. Then also
there's Coree, there's Coherent, there's
Nokia, there's Synopsis. There's this
interesting thing where there is kind of
like the circular economy type questions
going on where like okay Nvidia invests
in Core we have a Nebus then they take
that capital to buy Nvidia GPUs which
shows up as Nvidia revenue. They have
these companies on their cap table that
they are investing in and therefore
collecting revenue from. But I mean at
the end of the day this is kind of the
general play from the people who are in
the trenches in the world of AI. A lot
of infrastructure a lot of those like
higher level purchases into Intel into
SpaceX into the Neoclouds. uh that's
what they're thinking about. If you are
considering investing in this space, the
number one northstar you should always
ask yourself is will the demand for AI
products, AI tools, AI models be greater
10 years from now than it is today? If
your belief is yes, then all of these
things infrastructurally, especially
involved in physical atoms like GPUs,
like energy, like power is all going to
be required and going up. Now, of
course, you need to make sure that you
are backing the types of companies and
builders that are actually going to
execute on this. And when I think of
like the the dummies guide to to what to
to kind of like support, I look at
Nvidia's portfolio essentially because
they there's no one better than Jensen
Huang who has a much deeper insight as
to what is actually being built and
where the demand actually is. He said on
a recent uh I think it was like an
interview panel or maybe it was like at
one of these conferences that he spoke
at that people are questioning uh
whether some of these AI labs or some of
these hyperscalers are actually seeing
demand for the AI models and products
that they're offering like Microsoft and
Google for example prior to their
quarterly earnings everyone was doubting
them. Then they released their quarterly
earnings and not only has their revenue
gone up like 5x over the last quarter,
but they've also seen revenue margins
specifically go up and it's the same
trend that you see across Neoclouds,
hyperscalers, as well as some of these
CPU companies. So you see his biggest
position is a $30 billion stake in
Intel. Now, I want to remind everyone
that I think it was midway last year
that he put a $5 billion investment into
Intel to own I think it was like what
was it like a 5% stake in them. Uh he
invested alongside the US government and
the main reason for that was unclear at
the time but today is very clear. Intel
creates bleeding edge CPUs in order to
orchestrate all these hundreds of
thousands of GPUs. You need things like
CPUs to make sure that your AI agents
make the right tool calls and to make
sure that they operate efficiently and
fast enough for you to get your answer
to your prompt. And this is what all of
these companies are that Nvidia is
investing in. And you see this
collectively across so many of the
different phones. They're betting on AI
demand just being higher. And if that's
the case, then you're going to need more
Neoclouds. You're going to need more
hyperscalers. You are going to need way
more AI models. And you're going to need
a way to route across all of them.
You're going to need the power to like
power all of them. So this just makes a
lot of sense to me.
>> Yeah. No, it's pretty interesting. I
guess now we could kind of move down to
the like the rapidfire versions of just
like who who is left here. One of the
noteworthy investors, Bill Aman. We have
uh he is positioning himself mostly in
payments, which I find interesting. His
new positions are Visa, Mastercard, S&P
Global, and Netflix, which is a little
bizarre. And when you think about that
one, you're like, "Huh, why payments?"
And then you think, well, who did Stripe
just acquire? Um they just acquired Open
Router. It's like it turns out payment
infrastructure is due for an entire
overhaul and it seems like if you are
betting on that you're almost shorting
Visa and Mastercard uh not buying Visa
and Mastercard. So I'd love to talk
about why I'd love to ask him like why
are you going long these companies when
everybody's actively working to sabotage
and destroy them? Like the credit card
providers, for those who don't know,
they normally take an x amount of
pennies and like 2.9% 2.7% of every
transaction fairly large and a lot of
people are kind of sick of paying that.
And it seems like AA agents are needing
their own infrastructure lay in order to
make these payments. So I find the Visa
and Mastercard pretty interesting. Uh
there's a few other noteworthy ones.
There's um this guy Sam Clara who runs
apparently 35.4 billion worth of money.
His number one is Amazon. I mean, I it
seems like there's a lot of people in
Amazon being the number one. Tiger
Global, I think they had theirs as
number one. Also, David Ter, his number
one was Amazon. A lot of people are
really excited about Amazon. I'm just
looking at this and I'm seeing like a
lot of confusion. Like you've got Bill
Aman buying all the finance rail
companies, but he's trimming Amazon down
25%. Then you got Seth Clemen buying
Amazon. Then you got Terry Smith dumping
Visa, dumping dumping Alphabet. And so
I'm like, okay, like some of these funds
kind of agree with each other, some of
them don't. I think on your point around
why Aman might be buying like the
financial rails and why Stripe just
acquired Open Router. I'm realizing that
like the whole thesis of like plumbing
AI, I want to buy tokens and I want to
convert those tokens into intelligence
that makes my business earn more money.
Stripe is perfectly positioned for that.
Visa and Mastercard perfectly positioned
for that because they already have the
distribution to all of these different
companies financial books, right?
They're already getting paid. So for
them to flip on a switch and say, "Hey,
we can also provide you and serve you
the inference for all these different
models might actually be really
attractive." Maybe that's my tinpole hat
guess, but yeah. Well, all of these
things also require agents. And we're
going to have to talk about agents again
because of our friend and sponsor
Ledger, who is building an
infrastructure for agents in which
there's a three-part solution. The
agents propose, the humans approve, the
ledger signer enforces the transactions
that are being made. They built this
really neat Ledger agent stack that
allows you to use their open source
tools to work with agents because
chances are I mean if you're building
with agents you're pretty worried about
security. There's been a lot of
breakouts from companies like OpenAI and
Anthropic recently. You want to lock
that down. You do so with this hardware
process that Ledger has. They work with
cloud code. They work with codecs. It
works with cursor. It's all totally open
source for you to try out today. And you
can find more in the link in the
description below. Thank you to Ledger
for sponsoring this video. And as we get
to the final segment of the show, we
have to make the you have to answer the
question like, okay, what is the smart
money actually buying in consensus after
going through all these portfolios,
after seeing all these companies, what
are the largest winners and losers? And
we have this really nice chart on screen
for those who are watching on Spotify,
YouTube, wherever you get your videos,
it shows kind of where everyone's been
adding. And I see this line down the
board of Ter who seems to have added
like pretty much everything going across
the board. He's the new dude. Uh it
seems like Ter's like really making a
strong play into Amazon, Alphabet, TSMC,
Power Energy, Neocloud, SpaceX. But what
we do see is the most amount of dots out
of all these funds across Alphabet.
Everyone's really bullish on Google.
People want to own the company that's
spending how many hundreds of billions
of capex this year with how large profit
margins in their cloud infrastructure
with like a new leadership team that's
coming in probably a little more hungry
than the old. It seems like this new
beginning for Google almost. And the
hope is that a lot of people can
capitalize on that. The next most
popular, I guess there's three of them
here. It's Amazon, TSMC, and SpaceX.
Those all seem like pretty amazing
opportunities. Amazon, we know, is
pretty much one of the largest mag
companies for AI exposure. You get AWS,
you get the sneaky anthropic stake for
the company, and then you get tranium
chips, which are all three huge
verticals that can play a large role in
the earnings of Amazon. I think people
are pretty excited about these large cap
companies. SpaceX again goes without
saying we have 25 episodes on why
they're going to be one of the most
valuable companies in the world. People
are excited about AI data centers in
space. They're excited about Gro getting
on the frontier. They're excited about
the data center buildout. There's a lot
of things to be excited about there. And
then TSMC is just buying the picks and
shovels, man. Someone's got to make the
chips. TSMC is pretty damn good at it. I
think when we look at this, um, it gives
you a clear idea of where the consensus
of investments are in AI right now. Like
you look at Amazon and Alphabet, that's
not new news from like a couple years
back when these companies were making
very heavy capex investments in in in AI
in general. I still think that they have
a long way to go and I don't quite
believe people think uh that AI is going
to be as big as they could potentially
conceive. Like when I look at Andy
Jasse, CEO of Amazon's reports on AWS, I
can't help but think that I can't help
but get like incredibly bullish about it
because it's not only him making what is
it like a $200 billion investment this
year in AI Cabex, but it's him showing
us publicly, by the way, this is all
reported on the revenue and margins that
are expanding for the company itself. So
when you look at that and you look at
the investment, it kind of makes a lot
of sense. Bear in mind, Andy Jasse has
been running AWS well before he was CEO
of Amazon. So he knows the
infrastructure in and outs the best,
better than anyone, right? So when he
says things like this, it's it's very
important, I think, to pay attention.
Now, if you lower your gaze to to bottom
of this stack, it tells you where the
money is effectively going to go. It's
going to be in things like power and
energy. It's going to be in things like
payments and memory. Now, memory is
already quite a consensus trade, but as
you can see, a lot of people got scared
after the Leopold blowout. Now, is it
just a bl that was based off of leverage
or have we reached some kind of top that
maybe makes no sense? We're going to
have to see over the next couple of
months. It's my belief that like memory
is constrained by physical atoms. We do
not have enough plumbing and chip fabs
out there to meet demand going into
2028. I just want to emphasize all the
supply that is available for memory for
next year is completely sold out. You've
got SanDisk literally inventing brand
new forms of memory to be able to serve
up demand just to kind of get memory
into the hands of AI providers. Now,
when you look at payments, this is kind
of like a brand new thing. You know,
maybe we'll have a few more episodes in
the future about this, but you've got
Stripe just acquiring Open Router.
You've got RAMP creating their own
router. There's a lot of movement in the
AI router side of things, and that's a
thesis to unpack on a separate episode.
And then you have NeoClouds and power
and energy which has been the case for
so many years at this point where we
have all these GPUs. We're going to have
way more GPUs in the future and we don't
have enough power to surfer this. So
we're looking into nuclear, we're
looking into solar, we're looking into
ripping jet engines off planes and
trying to like spit it up at the back of
a data center, which is what Elon Musk
is literally doing. He bought a company
to help him do that. And so I think
we're going to see a bunch more of these
investments. Whether it pays out or
whether it plays out is something we're
going to see over the next couple of
months. It's my strong belief that we
will, but again, this could all be a
house of cards and a lot of people think
so and so I don't want to negate that
fact. Maybe
>> it's also worth noting that these aren't
uh specific AI filings for 13F
companies. Like these are just the
standard 13Fs. It just so happens that
it seems like a lot of the large funds
are investing in AI, which is
interesting is like if if everyone's
focused here, is there an edge
elsewhere? Is there some place that
other people aren't looking because
everyone is seemingly interested in
figuring out how this AI trade plays
out? Possibly. Probably. I don't see my
boys Tesla anywhere. Come on, where's
the love over there? But it's
interesting. It's interesting to think
like, hm, okay, well, if everyone's
focused on these things, is there an
edge? Is there alpha elsewhere that we
may be able to extract from the market?
Like the
>> It's interesting. No one's holding
Nvidia, Josh, like some of the like the
major company that's making these these
GPUs. Yeah, that was a Yeah, actually
Nvidia was missing from most of these,
huh? Except for I believe Gavin Baker
maybe uh has it as his largest holding.
I think he's Jensen's biggest bull. He
probably owns quite a bit. Warren
Buffett's still Bergkshire Hathway's
biggest holding is Apple. And I find it
ironic that it's been the biggest
holding forever. Um because everyone's
just kind of forgot about it. They've
moved past it. And yet Apple is
currently sitting here the most valuable
company in the world, even more so than
Nvidia. So it's it's pretty interesting
to see kind of how these companies
structure themselves. See which ones are
more nimble like Leopold and getting
blown out of their portfolios. Which
ones have been around since the
beginning of time like Birkshere and
they're actually just long some of these
fantastic companies that is now the most
valuable company in the world. And
perhaps you can use that to kind of
gauge your risk tolerance and see where
your personal portfolio fits into this.
Um but that is the entirety of the
episode today. I want to just thank
everyone so much for watching, for being
here with us, for hearing about the
aftermath of the uh Leopold blowup. I
thought this would be exciting for
different reasons, but um unfortunately
it is exciting because we get to see the
final holdings before everything
exploded. And now what you're looking at
is probably the Citadel portfolio
because they bought the entire thing in
a single block of trades. So
>> which they're up about 2 and a halfx
just FYI from that purchase.
>> Can you imagine? Oh my god.
>> 2 weeks. Also, didn't Leopold make like
a $500 million private investment? I I
saw it was reported on like Bloomberg or
Reuters or somewhere.
>> Yeah, man. He's down, but far from out.
He'll be back,
>> dude. He's already back. He's back.
Where did he get that cash?
>> It's going to You know what's going to
be really fun. You know what you really
need to stick around for is the next
Leva 13F because then we'll see what
rises from the ashes. It's like, okay,
like what is left? Is it going to be
zeroed? Is he even going to have enough
money on the balance sheet to be
required to file a 13F? We will see. I
suspect the answer will be yes. I
suspect it is a phoenix rising from the
ashes, a strong comeback. But that's the
update. If you enjoyed this episode, as
always, uh first, thank you so much for
watching. We really appreciate you
sticking around till the end. Second, uh
don't forget to share with a friend who
might also enjoy. Don't forget to give
us a thumbs up on YouTube or wherever
you view your podcast. Easy any final
parting thoughts before we head out of
here today? No, I uh I'm curious for the
folks who are listening who I I get are
very investor oriented. Are there any
layers of the stack or if there any
companies that we're missed? Like we
would love to to hear about it. Like
leave us in the comments uh a note, DM
us, whatever. We're always looking for
like where the edge might potentially
be. And you know, Josh and I have got
our rose tinted glasses on, right? We
love memory. We love PAL. We love
Nvidia. We love Google. So, uh if you
have any ideas, let us know. But that I
think is it. And yeah, we will see you
guys on the next one.